<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Melukote</string>

    <!-- Navigation Menu -->
    <string name="title_section1">About Melukote</string>
    <string name="title_section2">History</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Temple Info</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Places to Visit</string>
    <string name="title_section5">How to Reach</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Check Accommodation</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="P1_Para1"><![CDATA[Melukote in Pandavapura taluk of Mandya district, Karnataka, in southern India, is one of the sacred places in Karnataka. The place is also known as Thirunarayanapuram. It is built on rocky hills, known as Yadugiri, Yaadavagiri and Yadushailadweepa, overlooking the Cauvery valley. Melukote is about 51 km (32 miles) from Mysore and 133 km (83 mi) from Bangalore.]]></string>
    <string name="P1_Para2"><![CDATA[Melukote is the location of the Cheluvanarayana Swamy Temple, with a collection of crowns and jewels which are brought to the temple for the annual celebration. On the top of the hill is the temple of Yoganarasimha. Many more shrines and ponds are located in the town. Melukote is home to the Academy of Sanskrit Research, which has collected thousands of manuscripts.]]></string>
    <string name="P1_Para3"><![CDATA[Early in the 12th century, the famous Srivaishnava saint Sri Ramanujacharya, who hailed from Tamil Nadu, stayed at Melukote for about 12 years. It has thus become a prominent centre of the Srivaishnava sect.]]></string>

    <string name="P2_Title">History</string>
    <string name="P2_Para1"><![CDATA[Early in 12th century, the great Srivaishnava saint Sri Ramanuja took up his residence and lived in this location for about 14 years. It thus became a prominent centre of the Srivaishnava sect of Brahmins, who obtained from the Hoysala king Vishnuvardhana, who had become a follower of the Acharya, an assignment of the fertile tracts of land in the neighbourhood, especially of the Ashta Gramas, on either bank of the Cauvery.]]></string>

    <string name="P3_Title">Cheluvanarayana Swamy Temple</string>
    <string name="P3_Para1"><![CDATA[The principal temple is a square building of large dimensions but very plain, dedicated to Lord Cheluva-Narayana Swamy or Thirunarayana. The utsavamurthi, which is a metallic image, represents the deity who is called Shelvapillai, Cheluva Raya and Cheluvanarayana Swamy, whose original name appears to have been Ramapriya (meaning "Rama's Favourite"). It is believed that this utsavamurthi belonged to and was worshipped by Lord Rama and the kings of the surya vamsa Dynasty for generations.]]></string>

    <string name="P4_Title">Important places</string>

</resources>